A Guide to the Virginia District Pilot International records, 1947-2003
Library of Virginia
- Series VII: Pilot International Paper, 1989-1998., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 20-21)
  - Subseries 3: Pilot International Foundation, 1992-1996., 1 box (Box 21)
    - Papers, 1995-1996, no date. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 4: District Programs,., 1 box (Box 21)
    - Arkansas/Oklahoma District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Georgia District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Japan District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Kentucky-Ohio-West Virginia District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Alabama District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Alabama District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - California District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - California District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Florida District Fall Council, 1992. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Florida District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Florida District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Georgia District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Georgia Fall Council, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Kansas-Missouri District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Kansas-Missouri District convention,. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Kentucky-Ohio-West Virginia District Fall Council, 1993 (3 copies). (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Louisiana District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Louisiana District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Michigan-Indiana District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Midwest District convention, 1993 (2 copies). (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Mississippi Fall Council, 1992. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Mississippi District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - North Carolina District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Northeast-Potomac District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Northeast-Potomac District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - South Carolina District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Southwest District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Southwest District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Tennessee District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Tennessee District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Texas District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Texas District convention, 1994. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Western District convention, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 5: Directories, 1994-1996., 1 box (Box 21)
    - Directory, 1994-1995. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Directory, 1995-1996. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 6: General Files,., 1 box (Box 21)
    - Classification guide. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Pilot Log, 1995-1996. (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Series VIII: General Files and Ephemera., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 22-23)
  General Files and Ephemera contain papers concerning a reading program, brain injuries, and emergency response programs; certificates; patterns; stickers; and miscellaneous papers. Ephemera include Robert's Rules of Order, a brief-case, a 3-hole punch, and rubber stamps.
  - NASCO home reading program. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Brain disorders. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Lifeline, 1989-1990. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Certificates. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Cover design for 1995-1996 roster. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Forms and stationery. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - District badge patterns. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - State embroidery stickers. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous papers. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Robert's Rules of Order. (Box 22)
  - Briefcase labeled Governor, District 11 Pilot International. (Box 23)
  - Rubber stamps, 2 labelled BANQUET, 2 labelled BREAKFAST, 1 labelled LUNCHEON, and 1 labelled LUNCH. (Box 23)
  - 3-hole punch. (Box 23)
  - Award from Big Brothers/Big Sisters to the Pilot Club of Marion (see box 18 folder 1). (Box 23)
  - Charter of the Pilot Club of Marion (original--see box 15 folder 7), 28 February 1947. (Box 23)